A Guide to the Records of Julian A. Burruss, President, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1906-1946
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Series 3: Correspondence
  - Subseries 12: Correspondence, 1927
    - M.H. Eoff, 1927 (Box-folder 10-823)
    - Gordon Elean, 1927 (Box-folder 10-824)
    - J.B. Fogleman, 1927 (Box-folder 10-825)
    - Faculty Blanket Letters, 1927 (Box-folder 10-826)
    - F.H. Fish, 1927 (Box-folder 10-827)
    - L.E. Fuller, 1927 (Box-folder 10-828)
    - W.E. Garnett, 1927 (Box-folder 10-829)
    - James Gudkein, 1927 (Box-folder 10-830)
    - H.C. Groseclose, 1927 (Box-folder 10-831)
    - Harry Gudheim, 1927 (Box-folder 10-832)
    - Anna G. Hannas, 1927 (Box-folder 10-833)
    - M.C. Harrison, 1927 (Box-folder 10-834)
    - T.W. Hatcher, 1927 (Box-folder 10-835)
    - Heads of Departments, 1927 (Box-folder 10-836)
    - J. Marshall Hedrick, 1927 (Box-folder 10-837)
    - D.C. Heitshu, 1927 (Box-folder 10-838)
    - F.W. Hofmann, 1927 (Box-folder 10-839)
    - C.W. Holdaway, 1927 (Box-folder 10-840)
    - R.J. Holden, 1927 (Box-folder 10-841)
    - Katherine Holtzclaw, 1927 (Box-folder 10-842)
    - R.H. Hunt, 1927 (Box-folder 10-843)
    - R.E. Hussey, 1927 (Box-folder 10-844)
    - J.R. Hutcheson 1/1/27 - 6/30/27 (Box-folder 10-845)
    - J.R. Hutcheson 7/1/27 - 12/31/27 (2 folders) (Box-folder 10-846 to 10-847)
    - T.B. Hutcheson, 1927 (Box-folder 10-848)
    - M.L. Jefferies, 1927 (Box-folder 10-849)
    - V.O. Johns, 1927 (Box-folder 10-850)
    - J.S.A. Johnson, 1927 (Box-folder 10-851)
    - J.B. Jones, 1927 (Box-folder 11-852)
    - T.W. Knote, 1927 (Box-folder 11-853)
    - Lucy Lee Lancaster, 1927 (Box-folder 11-854)
    - C. Lee, 1927 (Box-folder 11-855)
    - J.B. Lucas, 1927 (Box-folder 11-856)
    - E.C. Magill, 1/1/27 - 6/30/27 (Box-folder 11-857)
    - J.P. Maloney, 1927 (Box-folder 11-858)
    - A.B. Massey, 1927 (Box-folder 11-859)
    - E.C. Miller, 1/1/27 - 6/30/27 (Box-folder 11-860)
    - C.P. Miles, 1927 (Box-folder 11-861)
    - W.R. Nichols, 1927 (Box-folder 11-862)
    - Louis O'Shaughnessy, 1927 (Box-folder 11-863)
    - J.J. Owens, 1927 (Box-folder 11-864)
    - C.M. Newman, 1927 (Box-folder 11-865)
    - G.W. Patteson, 1927 (Box-folder 11-866)
    - E.R. Price, 1927 (Box-folder 11-867)
    - H.L. Price, 1927 (Box-folder 11-868)
    - S.R. Pritchard, 1927 (Box-folder 11-869)
    - W.H. Rasche, 1927 (Box-folder 11-870)
    - H.B. Redd, 1927 (Box-folder 11-871)
    - Ellen A. Reynolds, 1927 (Box-folder 11-872)
      - Report - Proposed Five-Year Program for Research Work in Rural Child-Welfare in Virginia
    - F.L. Robeson, 1927 (Box-folder 11-873)
    - J.E. Williams, 1927 (Box-folder 11-874)
    - I.D. Wilson, 1927 (Box-folder 11-875)
    - T.K. Wolfe, Resigned 9/1/27 (Box-folder 11-876)
  - Subseries 13: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1927
    - Miscellaneous A, 1927 (Box-folder 11-877)
    - Miscellaneous B, 1927 (Box-folder 11-878)
    - J.H. Bradford, 1927 (Box-folder 11-879)
    - Harry Flood Byrd, Governor, 1927 (Box-folder 11-880)
    - Miscellaneous C, 1927 (Box-folder 11-881)
    - Miscellaneous D, 1927 (Box-folder 11-882)
    - M. J. Exner, 1927 (Box-folder 11-883)
    - Miscellaneous F, 1927 (Box-folder 11-884)
      - letter from Douglas S. Freeman
    - Miscellaneous G, 1927 (Box-folder 11-885)
    - Miscellaneous H, 1927 (Box-folder 11-886)
    - Norman Johnson, 1927 (Box-folder 11-887)
    - T. W. Knote, 1927 (Box-folder 11-888)
    - Miscellaneous L, 1927 (Box-folder 11-889)
    - Miscellaneous M, 1927 (Box-folder 11-890)
    - W.H. Manning, 1927 (Box-folder 11-891)
    - Miscellaneous N, 1927 (Box-folder 11-892)
    - Chas. A. Osborne, 1927 (Box-folder 11-893)
    - Miscellaneous P, 1927 (Box-folder 11-894)
    - Lawrence Priddy, 1927 (Box-folder 11-895)
    - Miscellaneous R, 1927 (Box-folder 11-896)
    - Miscellaneous S-T, 1927 (Box-folder 11-897)
    - B.H. Van Oot, 1927 (Box-folder 11-898)
    - Miscellaneous W, 1927 (Box-folder 11-899)
    - War Department, 1927 (Box-folder 11-900)
      - Gen. Douglas MacArthur letters which recognized VPI as a "Distinguished College"
  - Subseries 14: Correspondence, 1928
    - R.B.H. Begg, 1928 (Box-folder 11-901)
    - W.M. Brodie, 1928 (Box-folder 11-902)
    - R.M. Brown - Library, 1928 (Box-folder 11-903)
    - W.A. Brumfield, 1928 (Box-folder 11-904)
    - Reece L. Bryant, Poultry, 1928 (Box-folder 11-905)
    - F.A. Buchanan, 1928 (Box-folder 11-906)
    - O.C. Burkhart, 1928 (Box-folder 11-907)
    - T.P. Campbell, 1928 (Box-folder 11-908)
    - The Chaplains, 1928 (Box-folder 11-909)
    - Melria Chapman, 1928 (Box-folder 11-910)
    - W.B. Coggin, 1928 (Box-folder 11-911)
    - Clinton H. Cowgill, Professor of Architecture Eng., 1928 (Box-folder 11-912)
    - Mrs. M.M. Davis, Resigned, 1928 (Box-folder 11-913)
    - A.L. Dean, 1928 (Box-folder 11-914)
    - Paul B. Dick, Hygiene & Physical Education, 1928 (Box-folder 11-915)
    - Martha D. Dinwiddie, 1928 (Box-folder 11-916)
    - A.W. Drinkard, Jr., 1928 (Box-folder 11-917)
    - Faculty Blanket Letters, 1928 (Box-folder 11-918)
    - F.H. Fish - coal mining and coal usage, 1928 (Box-folder 11-919)
      - A report of the 2nd International Conference on Bituminous Coal, held at the Carnegie Institute of Tech, Pittsylvania, VA, 11/19/24, 1928
    - J.B. Fogleman, 1928 (Box-folder 11-920)
    - F.D. Fromme, 1928 (Box-folder 11-921)
    - W.E. Garnett, 1928 (Box-folder 11-922)
    - H.C. Groseclose, 1928 (Box-folder 11-923)
    - J.H. Hall, English, 1928 (Box-folder 11-924)
    - M.C. Harrison, 1928 (Box-folder 11-925)
    - H.H. Hill, 1928 (Box-folder 11-926)
    - Fred W. Hofmann, 1928 (Box-folder 11-927)
    - C.W. Holdaway, 1928 (Box-folder 11-928)
    - R.J. Holden, 1928 (Box-folder 11-929)
    - W.S. Hough, 1928 (Box-folder 11-930)
    - Hattie L. Hughes, 1928 (Box-folder 11-931)
    - Rueben L. Humbert, Exc. Sec. & Asst Prof Economics, 1928 (Box-folder 11-932)
    - R.E. Hunt, 1928 (Box-folder 11-933)
    - R.E. Hussey, 1928 (Box-folder 11-934)
      - Stream pollution
      - Pulp and paper
    - J.R. Hutcheson, Part 1, 1928 (Box-folder 11-935)
    - J.R. Hutcheson, Part 2, 1928 (Box-folder 11-936)
    - John R. Hutcheson 7/28 - 12/28 (2 folders) (Box-folder 11-937 to 11-938)
    - T.B. Hutcheson, 1928 (Box-folder 12-939)
    - M.L. Jefferies, 1928 (Box-folder 12-940)
    - J.S.A. Johnson, Professor, 1928 (Box-folder 12-941)
    - T.W. Knote, 1928 (Box-folder 12-942)
    - Claudius Lee, 1928 (Box-folder 12-943)
    - J. Elton Lodewick, Asso. Prof. Wood Technology, 1928 (Box-folder 12-944)
    - R.W. McNeil, Asst. Prof. English (Publications), 1928 (Box-folder 12-945)
    - E.C. Magill, 1928 (Box-folder 12-946)
    - A.B. Massey, 1928 (Box-folder 12-947)
    - R.G. Matheson, English, 1928 (Box-folder 12-948)
    - B.O. Miller, Instructor in Economics, 1928 (Box-folder 12-949)
    - E.C. Miller, 1928 (Box-folder 12-950)
      - Remodeling and repair of campus bldgs
    - E.C. Miller (Box-folder 12-950A)
      - Troy Simmons Case - fatally injured by fall at Memorial Building
      - Petition for building tennis courts by faculty
      - Fire in barracks
      - William Hoge case - stealing
      - Purchase of property adjoining VPI
    - C.P. Miles - Athletics, 1928 (Box-folder 12-951)
    - Margaret Minnis, 1928 (Box-folder 12-952)
    - S.R. Minter, 1928 (Box-folder 12-953)
    - C.A. Montgomery, 1928 (Box-folder 12-954)
    - A.V. Morris, 1928 (Box-folder 12-955)
    - C.M. Newman, 1928 (Box-folder 12-956)
    - Wm. R. Nichols, 1928 (Box-folder 12-957)
    - E.B. Norris, Dean of Engineering, 1928 (Box-folder 12-958)
    - Louis O'Shaughnessy, 1928 (Box-folder 12-959)
    - J.J. Owens, 1928 (Box-folder 12-960)
    - E.R. Price, 1928 (Box-folder 12-961)
    - H.L. Price, 1928 (Box-folder 12-962)
    - S.R. Pritchard, 1928 (Box-folder 12-963)
    - W.R. Rasche, 1928 (Box-folder 12-964)
    - Paul M. Reanes, Instructor Dairy Husbandry, 1928 (Box-folder 12-965)
    - H.B. Redd, 1928 (Box-folder 12-966)
    - Allan H. Reid, Landscape, 1928 (Box-folder 12-967)
    - H.B. Riffenberg, Chemistry, 1928 (Box-folder 12-968)
    - W.J. Schoene, 1928 (Box-folder 12-969)
    - C.E. Seitz, 1928 (Box-folder 12-970)
    - F.L. Watson, 1928 (Box-folder 12-971)
    - J.W. Watson, 1/1/28 - 1/1/29 (Box-folder 12-972)
    - John W. Whittemore, Prof. Ceramic Engineering, 1928 (Box-folder 12-973)
    - J. Henry Wild, Asst. Prof. Of German & French, 1928 (Box-folder 12-974)
    - J.E. Williams, 1928 (Box-folder 12-975)
    - C.R. Wooline, Jr., Health Officer, 1928 (Box-folder 12-976)
  - Subseries 15: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1928
    - Miscellaneous A-B, 1928 (Box-folder 12-977)
    - W.E. Bell, Jr. - hazing, 1928 (Box-folder 12-978)
    - J.H. Bradford, 1928 (Box-folder 12-979)
    - Harry F. Byrd, Governor, 1928 (Box-folder 12-980)
    - Miscellaneous C-D, 1928 (Box-folder 12-981)
    - Hon. Westmoreland Davis, 1928 (Box-folder 12-982)
    - Paul N. Derring, 1928 (Box-folder 12-983)
    - Miscellaneous E-G, 1928 (Box-folder 12-984)
    - Miscellaneous H-M, 1928 (Box-folder 12-985)
    - W.H. Manning, 1928 (Box-folder 12-986)
    - Miscellaneous N, 1928 (Box-folder 12-987)
    - G.L. Noble/Copper - Ketcham Bill, 1928 (Box-folder 12-988)
    - Chas. A. Osborne, 1928 (Box-folder 12-989)
    - Miscellaneous P, 1928 (Box-folder 12-990)
    - Lawrence Priddy, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 12-991)
    - Miscellaneous R-S, 1928 (Box-folder 12-992)
    - G.R. Spitzer, 1928 (Box-folder 12-993)
    - Miscellaneous T-V, 1928 (Box-folder 12-994)
    - B.H. Van Oot, 1928 (Box-folder 12-995)
    - Miscellaneous W, 1928 (Box-folder 12-996)
    - War Department, 1928 (Box-folder 12-997)
  - Subseries 16: Correspondence, 1929
    - T.J. Allen, 1929 (Box-folder 12-998)
    - G.J. Baird, 1929 (Box-folder 12-999)
    - R.B.H. Begg, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1000)
    - W.M. Brodie, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1001)
    - R. M. Brown, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1002)
      - Aesthetic atmosphere of VPI
      - Library matters
      - Bibliography of VPI publications
      - The Lyric Poetry Magazine
    - F.A. Buchanan, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1003)
    - W.H. Byrne, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1004)
    - Clinton H. Cowgill, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1005)
    - Clinton H. Cowgill, 1929-1930 (Box-folder 12-1005A)
    - P.S. Dear, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1006)
    - Martha D. Dinwiddie, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1007)
    - A.W. Drinkard, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1008)
    - M.H. Eoff, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1009)
    - Faculty Blanket Letters, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1010)
    - F.H. Fish, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1011)
    - J.B. Fogleman, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1012)
    - W.E. Garnett, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1013)
      - Rural church conference-short course for rural church ministers
      - Virginia rural church survey report; study of church, organization, conditions, problems and relation to the state
    - H.C. Groseclose, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1014)
      - Agricultural high school rally to build attendance to V.P.I.
    - M.C. Harrison, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1015)
    - F.W. Hofmann, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1016)
    - C.W. Holdaway, 1929 (Box-folder 12-1017)
    - R.J. Holden, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1018)
      - Virginia coal operators and geological survey in regard to reclassification under anthracite
      - Moving picture films shown at Lyric theatre; discussion of a firm in Chicago to add dialogue to make a talking picture
      - Proposed hydro-electric plant on New River
      - Radford water power development
    - Rueben L. Humbert, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1019)
    - R.E. Hunt, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1020)
      - Proposed cavalry unit, acquisition of horses and building of barns
    - R.E. Hussey, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1021)
      - Stream pollution project/committee meeting
    - John R. Hutcheson - Part 1, 1/1/29 - 12/31/29 (Box-folder 13-1022)
      - Consideration of a school for ministers
      - Federal Capper Ketcham Act
      - Book of Dr. John D. Black
      - Housing for unmarried women on campus of V.P.I.
      - Construction of new dormitories/overcrowding
    - John R. Hutcheson - Part 2, 1/1/29 - 12/31/29 (Box-folder 13-1023)
      - Preparation of young women (agents) for home demonstration work
    - T.B. Hutcheson, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1024)
    - M.L. Jeffries, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1025)
    - J.S.A. Johnson, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1026)
    - Dayton M. Kohler, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1027)
    - T.W. Knote, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1028)
    - J. Elton Ladewick, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1029)
    - Claudius Lee, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1030)
    - R.H. McNeil, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1031)
      - Making arrangements for radio broadcasting
    - E.C. Magill, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1032)
      - Organization of Alpha Zeta chapter
      - George-Reed bill passes the Senate
    - Frank Marshall, Jr., 1929 (Box-folder 13-1033)
    - Major John B. Maynard, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1034)
      - Importance of chemistry in future warfare; possible establishment of a chemical warfare service unit of the R.O.T.C.
      - Possible aviation unit of the R.O.T.C.
    - C.P. Miles, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1035)
    - E.C. Miller, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1036)
    - F.A. Motz, Resigned, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1037)
    - C.M. Newman, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1038)
    - Wm. R. Nichols, Transferred, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1039)
    - E.B. Norris, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1040)
    - Louis O'Shaughnessy, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1041)
    - J.J. Owens, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1042)
    - P.B. Potter, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1043)
    - E.R. Price, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1044)
    - H.L. Price, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1045)
    - S.R. Pritchard, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1046)
    - H.B. Redd (Box-folder 13-1047)
    - Allan H. Reid, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1048)
    - R.A. Runnels, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1049)
    - Miscellaneous - S, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1050)
    - Philip C. Scherer, Jr., 1929 (Box-folder 13-1051)
    - C.E. Seitz, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1052)
    - Francis J. Sette, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1053)
    - A.E. Shannon, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1054)
    - Maude E. Wallace (Box-folder 13-1055)
    - J.W. Watson, 1/1/29 (Box-folder 13-1056)
    - Emma S. Weld, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1057)
    - John W. Whittemore, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1058)
    - J.E. Williams, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1059)
    - T.D. Wilson, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1060)
    - S.A. Wingard, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1061)
    - C.R. Woolwine, Jr., 1929 (Box-folder 13-1062)
  - Subseries 17: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1929
    - Miscellaneous A-B, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1063)
    - H.K. Bowen, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1064)
    - J.H. Bradford, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1065)
    - Hon. James P. Buchanan, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1066)
    - Julian Burruss, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1067)
      - Acknowledgements, letters from the governor
      - Blanket letters--State Agriculture Commission
    - Gov. Harry F. Byrd, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1068)
    - Gov. Harry F. Byrd--Commission Matters, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1069)
    - Miscellaneous C-D, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1069)
    - Paul N. Derring, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1070)
    - Miscellaneous F, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1071)
    - Miscellaneous G, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1072)
    - Miscellaneous H, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1073)
    - G. F. Halsinger, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1074)
    - Miscellaneous K, 1929 (Box-folder 13-1075)
    - Miscellaneous L-M, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1076)
    - Major Richard Messer, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1077)
    - Hon. W. Stuart Moffett, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1078)
    - Miscellaneous N, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1079)
    - J. V .Nichols, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1080)
    - Miscellaneous O-P, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1081)
      - Merrimac Mines and local coal production
      - John Lester - notorious bootlegger and the sale of alcohol in Blacksburg as it relates to the cadets
    - Dr. Clarence Poe, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1082)
    - Miscellaneous Q, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1083)
    - Miscellaneous R, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1084)
    - Miscellaneous S, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1085)
      - Transfer of Smith-Lever Extension Work for Negroes from Hampton Institute to the Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute
    - Miscellaneous T, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1086)
    - Edward G. Tankard, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1087)
    - Hon A. J. Terrell, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1088)
    - Senator S. J. Thompson, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1089)
    - Jesse Urquhart, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1090)
    - Miscellaneous V-W, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1091)
    - Senator J. B. Watkins, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1092)
    - Hon. H. K. Whitehead, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1093)
    - T.K. Wolfe, 1929 (Box-folder 14-1094)
  - Subseries 18: Correspondence, 1930
    - E.J. Albert, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1095)
    - R.B.H. Begg, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1096)
      - Drill field Water Drainage
      - Establishment of Traffic Bureau offices at the Bristol TN, VA Chamber of Commerce
      - Reduction of coal freight rates
    - Col. W.M. Brodie, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1097)
    - R.M. Brown, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1098)
    - Chaplains, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1099)
      - Outline of a short course for rural ministers
    - Clinton H. Cowgill, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1100)
    - The Deans, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1101)
      - Financial assistance due to business depression
    - Martha D. Dinwiddie, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1102)
      - Women students access to books and housing
      - Rural home development committee
    - A.W. Drinkard, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1103)
    - Paul B. Dyck, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1104)
    - M.H. Eoff, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1105)
    - Faculty Blanket Letter, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1106)
    - F.H. Fish, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1107)
    - Miscellaneous - G, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1108)
    - W.E. Garnett, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1109)
    - W.S. Gay, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1110)
    - H.S. Grenoble, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1111)
    - Henry C. Groseclose, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1112)
    - Harry Gudheim, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1113)
    - C.W. Holdaway, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1114)
      - Announcement of short courses in connection with farm and educational work
      - Erection of dairy products building
    - R.J. Holden, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1115)
    - R.L. Humbert, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1116)
    - R.E. Hunt, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1117)
    - J.R. Hutcheson 1/1/30 - 7/1/30 (Box-folder 14-1118)
    - John R. Hutcheson 7/1/30 - 12/30/30 (Box-folder 14-1119)
      - Discussion of Federal Assistance to farmers due to poor weather Conditions
      - Discussion of making the Institute of Rural Affairs national in scope
      - Broadcasting Program Radio Station
      - Growth of Flax
    - T.B. Hutcheson, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1120)
    - J.S.A. Johnson, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1121)
    - T.W. Knote, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1122)
      - Consideration of Graduate Work in the Department of Business Administration
    - Claudius Lee, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1123)
    - J.E. Lodewick, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1124)
    - R.H. McNeil, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1125)
      - Planning of Celebration for 60th Anniversary of V.P.I.
      - Continued Discussion of Broadcast Station
    - E.C. Magill, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1126)
    - J.B. Maynard, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1127)
    - R.D. Michael, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1128)
    - C.P. Miles, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1129)
      - Discussion of Sports at Virginia Tech
      - Building Sporting Venue Infrastructure
      - Budget Outline
    - E.C. Miller, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1130)
      - Architectural Sketches of Fish Cottage
      - Building Upgrades
      - Fire at Dr. Garnett's Residence
    - Maragaret Minnis, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1131)
    - C. M. Newman, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1132)
    - E. B. Norris, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1133)
    - Louis O'Shaughnessy, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1134)
    - J. J. Owens, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1135)
    - E. R. Price, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1136)
      - Announcement of Radio Programs for October 1 through December 31, 1930
    - H. L. Price, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1137)
    - H. B. Redd, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1138)
      - Virginia Tech enrollment numbers
    - Miscellaneous - T, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1139)
      - Ohio College Association Bulletin
    - Miscellaneous - U, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1140)
    - Miscellaneous - V, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1141)
    - B. H. Van Oot, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1142)
      - Capper-Reed Vocational Education Bill
      - H.R. 10821
    - J. E. Williams, 1930 (Box-folder 21-1518)
    - Miscellaneous - W, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1143)
    - War Department, 1930 (Box-folder 14-1144)
      - ROTC Survey
      - Special Orders
    - J. W. Watson, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1145)
    - John W. Whittemore, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1146)
    - W. E. Wine, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1148)
    - T. K. Wolfe, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1149)
    - Miscellaneous, X, Y, Z, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1150)
      - Conference on Adult Education
      - Celebration of the centennial of the invention of the reaper by Cyrus Hall McCormick
  - Subseries 19: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1930
    - Miscellaneous - A, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1151)
    - Miscellaneous - B, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1152)
      - Water power development
    - Lawrence T. Berry, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1153)
    - H.K. Bowen, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1154)
    - Donaldson Brown, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1155)
      - Anticipated growth patterns
      - Expressed need of new facilities
    - J.H. Bradford, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1156)
      - Total student enrollment record
    - Miscellaneous - C, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1157)
      - Letter in opposition to war
      - "Proposal is to delegalize war by making its prohibition a basic principle of international law by an enactment accomplished by a conference or negotiation or by a congress of nations."
    - W.E. Carson, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1158)
    - Miscellaneous - D, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1159)
      - Open letter of confidence to President Hoover
      - Letters from Alfred DuPont
      - Letter from National Woman's Christian Temperance Union in concern of drinking among American college undergraduates
    - Paul M. Derring, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1160)
    - Miscellaneous - E, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1161)
      - Transfer of extension work from Hampton Institute to the State College
    - Miscellaneous - F, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1162)
    - J.P. Fishburn, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1163)
    - Miscellaneous - G, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1164)
      - Proposed short course for rural ministers and other church workers
    - Miscellaneous - H, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1165)
      - Roerich museum proposed international flag for protection of museums, cathedrals, libraries, and universities
    - Miscellaneous - I, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1166)
    - Miscellaneous - J, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1167)
      - Patrick Henry bust for the Hall of Fame: New York University
    - T.C. Johnson, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1168)
      - Work Report of the Virginia Truck Experiment Station
    - J. Ambler Johnston, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1169)
    - Miscellaneous - K, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1170)
    - George W. Koiner, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1171)
    - Miscellaneous - L, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1172)
    - Miscellaneous - M, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1173)
    - Warren H. Manning Offices/Eglert Hans, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1174)
    - Manufacturer's Records/Blue Book/etc., 1930 (Box-folder 15-1175)
      - Blue Book of Southern Progress
    - J.H. Meek, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1176)
    - Major Richard Messer, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1177)
    - Miscellaneous - N, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1178)
    - W.S. Newman, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1179)
    - Miscellaneous - O, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1180)
    - Miscellaneous - P, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1181)
      - Report on the teaching of psychology
    - Dr. J.G. Pollard, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1182)
    - Miscellaneous - Q, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1183)
      - Inquiry by a "group of colored people who would like to establish a training school for their race."
    - Miscellaneous - R, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1184)
      - Mechanical engineering library
    - Major A.W. Robertson, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1185)
      - Pond and fish inquiries
      - Issues of stream pollution
    - R.I. Roop College Attorney, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1186)